[Music]
Singh And finally, the
discussions about the market's risk,
when will Nifty break 18500, for how long will it
remain in consolidation,
why does Nifty return after reaching 1800 and then 18400, and
how much time will it take, did not end. But today we
saw that the market's pace was
quite impressive on the first trading day of the week and the
week started off quite well.
Nifty opened above 18619 and then appeared to hit a high of 18641.
However, if seen from the upper source, there
is definitely a decline of 40 points to 41 points. Below 18600, at this time, the
star of 18599 is visible. But
if we look at the overall, the market's direction is
largely positive. Out of 50 Nifty cities, there are
33 cities which are
operating strongly and Mahesh, there are 17 cities
where such decline is being seen.  Is
Nifty ready for the highs? Now,
how should a strategy be made in the market? How should
stocks be selected because many are at
52-week highs. So, from
here, a rally will be seen in bullish stocks.
I will talk to you about all this for the next one hour. But
in today's strength, the sectors which are
looking the strongest and are participating in the best way,
today we are seeing that there is considerable strength in banking,
whether it is banks or
companies related to financial services, there is strength in all of them.
Metal is once again
seen shining. Apart from this,
good buying is being seen in PSU banks. Today,
Bank Nifty has reached a
record high of 4483. Bank Nifty has not reached that high,
so there is continuous strength being seen in banking.
As
we were just telling you, Nifty
made a high of 641, 600, just a little bit, but 641. So, there is
considerable strength being seen here.
Continuous buying is being seen in consumer durables.
We also discussed this on Friday. Are there any reasons
and there is potential to see even more strength here now.
So let's talk about all these aspects.
Now let's talk to today's guest.
Arun Mantri has
joined us. Today's special guest is
Founder Mantri, then Arun ji of MA.
Many thanks and congratulations. Welcome to today
's program. Today
when the market is at this stage that if it goes
above 18600 then it will run. Now it has become just a
game of numbers.
Nifty has also chosen its Rustam Rustam.
Bank Nifty has already got its
midcap index. New highways are functioning, so it is
just a game of numbers and
how are you seeing the direction of the market from here.
Good afternoon, we got to
see clear results, after which we were talking about the same thing last week
also that after the expiry of last week,
whatever position has been taken, it has become weak
and the market was
more in the new zoom series, you got to
see the clear result of this in Nifty.  I would
definitely like to share one data with you, the
time brother has already said that the index is
also with my brother and Nifty is
also at 200.2 but the small cap
index is also around 10000, its
ultra is above ₹12000, which means that the
steam that is still left is Nifty
small trading and some is
also left in Nifty midcap, so I am thinking that it is
clearly a numbers game, I am thinking that
in three to four days, if we talk about global markets being
stable because today its
market band is in the evening, its
markets will open only tomorrow and if the global markets are stable,
then you can see the level of 800 this week,
sir, the level of 18,800 can be
seen this week, sir,
but when the market is standing at a new high, then what
should be the approach, should we be a
little scared from here or do you think that
it will break like this now, so now the market has been in a
dare for a long time,
remained on the ground, many international  The signals
that were being received were negative, so will there be
more chances of further rise in the future
or should we proceed with a little trial approach?
Absolutely, if it is a short term trade, if you are trading at a
low market price, if the market price is
near the time limit, if there is a short term trade, then you should
definitely pay attention to the levels. The
short term levels are visible on the technical chart,
whether it is a market do trade
or you are trading and
your position levels are exited in the market from the intraday level every day,
because your trade is a
big mouth, a big structure has already been formed, the
structure is still looking very good,
so definitely pay attention to the levels, until the
market settles below 18000, if the
level of 300 does not break back below the level of 18350,
which has become a base, then
you will continue to transact in the market,
no doubt then the positions have become very heavy
long, around 65% have been long,
which is a sign of option,
but I feel that there will
not be much decline in the market, it is possible that we may
see consolidation, but if it comes back down  If the
market reaches 400, it will be
great. So for short term credit, you
definitely have to follow the levels.
For long term, again, we have been talking for many weeks
that your ship must continue
and you should
not buy frontline stocks at every ground. So,
in the recent decline, you should buy the strong stocks, the frontline
stocks and the unfazed stocks.
Come on, many Darshans are
asking their questions together and
we would like to
discuss the answers to their questions with you one by one.
First of all, Darshan, who has sent us the question, has
come from YouTube. He has created
his YouTube ID in the name of Real Truth Seeker
and is looking to know your views on latent
and he has latent shares at 414. Right now,
if we look at this, the latter is
working with the ground around it. A star of 328 is
visible here and if we talk about the entire 1 year, then it is
working in a dare,
sir, but his purchases have been
seen in the last 1 year.  They have not got
much meaning for the work being done in Dare.
What are you telling them, this
gap of 52 to 422 and their buying at 414 near it.
Vipul ji, the overall results were much
below the market expectation, due to which
you are also seeing selling in the stock.
If you also see the data of last 8 or 9 days, the
momentum that has come in the market, that
momentum has not been seen in the stock, so it is
clearly a witness that no doubt in the stock,
its price is around the peak of time hi or you
can say, so I
felt that they should definitely maintain Stock Plus
because the stock is performing inside,
if the market falls, then their stock can
fall more rapidly,
hence do Stock Plus, Stock Plus,
put Stock Plus of 305 which is below the recent low
which was made
in March 2023, I am giving the low below that only, so
if the stock goes below 305 then it is
butter, you should exit because
if  If it keeps performing inside then even if the market
goes up you will not make money in the stock,
so put a stock plus of 305, it may take a
lot of time for your price to come back
because the results were below
expectations, the technical structure is
not doing well, the stock is good,
you can reduce it by 30%,
if that level is broken then
exit the stock, right in the meantime a question has come from Raghav ji
and he wants to know
what should be the entry point in Tarzan product
and at the same time he also wants to know that
in the short term,
that is, in the future, can this Tarzan product give me a return of 10%
in a short period, can
Tarzan product, when the market is doing so well, then
sir should
we try to take the trend towards midcap and small cap
or should we keep it on the frontline, Tashan
product, right now a rise of around 100% is being
seen here, talking about today's trading,
10 years are expecting a return of 10%, from
around 8%, 800  The lion was seen falling,
see your opinion on this city, by the way, if you ever look at the overall trend of the market
or if people
ever look at the sentiment, then first the
bank which has come has almost
come in the large cap, second a little bit in the midcap world cap,
that spread has been seen and it has been seen, so
I am liking it, there is still some stem
left in the small cap, as far as Tarzan is concerned,
I am liking this stock, it has already given a big breakout,
stop above 570,
so if you want to buy for the short term, then you
can definitely do it, first do it for the
topless because the
volumes are low, not high, if the
sentiment in the market gets even a little bad then there is a big T in the stock,
so keep that thing in your mind
that the volume in the stock is low and if the
market falls then a little more T will be seen, you
can buy by bringing a stop at 570 and proceed with the buy, 620 625, these two targets are
visible to me in the short term, a
return of 8 to 10% is not visible at the moment  This is
happening but you should definitely
take cooperation from the other side after seeing the return of 3 to 4 percent in the stock and this is
Sakshi ji's question. Sakshi ji has two
questions, sir, she wants to know about Adani Wilmar,
what should be the entry level.
Now if we look at it today, there is a
ground of around half a percent here and the
immense circuit which was looking for a shoulder in a way,
seems to be holding a bit, so is it possible to enter at these levels now?
You are feeling that so much has
already run away, collection has started
coming slowly, now we should wait and
secondly, they have identified IDA Services
for entry,
so what should Sakshi ji enter? If we
talk about Adani Services group, there are only two
i.e. Apurti and Angura Cement, I
felt that if they want to remain in the Adani group, then it is
better that you are sitting on Ambuja Cement,
which will get you a price around 10%, you will
not have to spend any capital and if you have
not entered Adani Wilmar, then
you can enter Ambuja Cement
around 430  If you get any stock,
you can buy Ambuja Cement. Buy the
stock of four one five plus.
I am still seeing it at the level of 4507
in Adani Ambuja Cement.
As far as the details are concerned,
its structure is strong.
Ideal Vijay, if you want to buy, you
can do it at the current level as well because the
overall finance sector is doing well and the
broking company is also expected to give good results,
which you can manage the market.
You may see a good trend in the coming two.
Bring a stoppage of 60-6, brother, open at 75-76. This
target is for you to see in your heart. Okay,
next Darshan, the people who have joined us are
Avinash ji and Sakshi ji,
if I go for cement in your place, it will be
better for you. But
today, hello,
very good. Stay happy.
Tell me what is your question. Sir, today
you bought at 3431. Just now,
after that, there were a
lot of incidents like bonus and split in it.
Perhaps
I found this a good company for such a fund for the long term.  Right now I am
running at par
but I have not received any appreciation. They
ask me what would be your advice here, should I
hold or not,
Sir, he has held shares of Hero MotoCorp
and he has been holding them since 2015 for a long time,
what should he do now, he
bought them at Rs. 3400 and right now he is in loss,
which is a little, but he is getting dividends,
we had seen that Sir, a good rally
was seen in this around 2017
when we had held shares from around Rs. 4000
and after that a lot of
collection was seen, there has been a lot of ups and downs,
but till now he has not got the price
and it has been five and seven years since he has been holding them for 8 years,
your opinion,
he has held them since 2015, I
think he has got dividend 15 to 18 times
in this stock, according to the
data I am seeing,
if we include the dividend, then the cost to me will be
around Rs. 50  It can go down to Rs 100 or below. It happens that
very good results have also come and it is
trading around its good level.
If they can add capital then they
can also make average income. I am thinking that the
stock can go back to Rs 3000 but you can
see it happening as soon as the monsoon season starts
or our season starts. I think the
stock will do very well and the stock can
go up to Rs 3000 or Rs 3200. The
overall results are very strong. The
sales of local to wheeler which were decreasing in the past are
also very good. So
hold the stock. If you want to average it then you can add
10 to 12 shares and also at the current level. If the
overall price of everything goes down then
I think they should hold the stock.
I am getting a target of Rs 3100.
In the medium term, the stock should come in. We
can see it going beyond Rs 3100. In the midst of all this, let me
tell you that if you also have any question related to your city, please
ask me.  You too are
not understanding what targets should be set in your city,
should you place stop losses, then
join us. All you have to do is
pick up your mobile phone and
WhatsApp 931121874.
This is our WhatsApp number through which you
can connect with us. You can
talk to our special guest today and that minister.
So keep sending us your questions.
If you are looking for a middle position in the mill,
you
can reach us at inquiry@tv9.com. But whatever question you
send, send it to Star Plus. How many shares have you not
held, at what price have you held them, for how
long can you hold them, what is your view,
short term or long term. If
you send it with all these details, then
we will answer your questions in as much detail as possible.
Now let's take the next Darshan question.
Aryan Rathore has sent us a question
and Aryan's question here is
regarding Piramal Pharma. Arun ji, you
probably asked a question on Piramal Pharma before as well, so
okay, let's discuss it one more time today.
He has bought 3000 shares, his purchase is of 105,
regarding Sir Gramel Pharma, this share
broke very fast and after that the
recovery was also seen here, he
bought it at 105 but still there is a fair distance from his purchase,
right now he is incurring a loss of 23-24 rupees, so
this fall,
after the fall, there was a rally and a lot of correction from above, from
around 3:45 you can see how it
corrected, although the recovery that came was for
one or two days, it was not a very sharp
recovery, what should be done, in this recovery, the
price of 8082 is being seen, should we take it out
or should we hold it now, it has been
seen for the last one week, so you will find this
stock in the portfolio of many retailers,
after Dhimazar,
you will also see the company in the portfolio of many people, keep
one thing in mind in this stock,
definitely maintain Stock Plus because the
base formation has just happened, now a
complete base formation has to be made on the chart, so
of 75  Be sure to keep an eye on the stock; it
can go up to 9697. There
is a resistance around this point and
a big gap is also visible around there on the technical chart,
so it can go up to 9697.
If the police continues in the market and
please continue with conservation, then the levels of 95 to 97 can be
reached, but definitely keep a shortcut of 75.
If the stock goes back below 75, then a
big fall is expected in this stock.
Many of
our households are asking, Sir, please
tell me a couplet that will do well in the future. Sir,
you keep watching the program and some people are also asking,
where can we invest today? So,
we have taken two couplets from Arun ji and we will
discuss them in detail at the end of the program. The
last 10 minutes will be very
important, so stay tuned and
we are continuously discussing your questions, so
discussions on this will continue.
Meanwhile, Shyam Sundar will take the question of the next darshan.
Gupta ji's
question has come. Good afternoon Arun ji,
good afternoon Vipul ji, thank you very much
Sir Shyam Sundar ji for asking his question.
He is saying whether
investment can be made in NMDC Steel. At which star can
investment be made? Can it be made at the current star? The
question is regarding NMDC. Sir, there is a recovery in metal today,
we are seeing that it has been going on for a long time,
especially the international
conditions that are being seen, the
current price of 107 is maintained at this time, will it continue? A
little collection is not being seen, it has been under
pressure since January,
see and if it is long term, not short term,
if it is not for one to two months, then you can
definitely add me and move ahead. I am
seeing this stock near 107 108, it
is around a good phase, but avoid it for short term trading
because short term, there is still a
trade left, so avoid it for short term trading.
Long term, if you have a little longer
view, then definitely add it and
below the level of 102 103.  If we get it, we can
add more and move ahead because the company
is good. Because the prices of iron ore have geared up a bit,
due to this, some pressure is being seen in the stock.
But as soon as the
overall metal sector picks up, this
stock can also do well. So, between 102 to 107, there are
strong support zones gradually around it. If
we look at the long term, then I am going to see
these levels of 125-120 there. Let us see you again in the open.
Meanwhile, Jatin Chauhan ji has
asked a question, hello sir, can I
invest in Vector Foods today? I
am a beginner, so I can only make a small investment. I have a
long term view. I
want to invest Rs 10,000. Should I wait or
buy it now? He has identified Vector Foods, he is a
new applicant,
he has collected Rs 10,000 from the story
and he is looking to invest in it for the long term.
Currently, it is trading at Rs 79192.
Today, there has been a huge rally, there has been a
rally of more than 10%.  Sir,
after this huge rally in Doctor Food, are there any
possibilities emerging, the
stock is trending around the time hi, it is near the 52 level,
what would be your advice, sir, is it
right to buy at the 52 level or should we wait,
Vipul ji, you have done a good job,
your profile has clearly
stated that he is a new investor, he wants to invest
his second amount in only one stock
or it is the first time, as I
understood, he
wants to invest for the first time, so one advice would definitely be this,
JB, if you are a new investor or
you are investing new money in the market, if you are
investing for the first time, then
keep two alternatives, either you
invest in the frontline last step which is Nifty 50
stock or
you can invest directly and indirectly in mutual funds, so
Vector Food, the stock which has already gone up to
480, has
come almost around 8 in the short term, so I should
avoid this stock, if you want to invest in it, if you want to invest
in the market, if you want to invest in direct equity, then it
is butter  You can put Frontline stock
in any bank,
whether it is SBI or
ICC,
put your amount of Rs 10,000 there because
you are an investor,
you will not be able to send it, hence it is butter, stay
away from midcap small pack for now, if you want to
put it in the last step then
put it in Frontline bags, SBI
channel can tell me on any channel, you can divide it and put it
in all three, so butter or
front line, especially vector food should be
provided because the stock is already
moving from ₹300 to ₹400, already make a
statement,
but sir, those who have bought it and
who are looking at the 52 week high, should
they put a training stop loss, the
company's results came on the 25th and
we saw that the company's profit is 170% bigger
and it was 170% bigger at Rs 27.6 crore, the company
also gave a good dividend,
how are you looking at the
company overall and is there any Fortuner for those who are Nivedita and those who are
experienced players  Is there a
settlement or should there be
distance after such a rally like this, the
stock is
moving around, so butter, your
training is kept slightly above its price, it
is definitely around the 650 level of the IPO price, even now the momentum of the training stoppage is
quite big, the stock has gained
almost 20 to 22% momentum in the last 3 days, so
your training below 680,
until the 680 level is not broken,
you can enjoy the upward rally and move on as you go, in the
meantime there are some booming stocks and
due to a little time constraint,
we will not be able to discuss many stocks, today
we would like to discuss one or two stocks, the graphic is
first of all, it is made by a single company,
so we brought it forward and
we saw the results of ICC Lombard and the news is here, the
results of the waiver, the news is that
such banks have a
big share in such Lombard till the tax fishes and the company plans to increase it
and even after this we saw that a
good momentum was seen  achieved and at the same time
many achieved their goals
Motilal Oswal has increased the target on ICC Lombard. Now Motilal Oswal has
increased its target on this company to 1400 and in the
initial market which was 17, we
saw that a rise of up to 14% was seen here, so
due to the news, a jump of up to 14% was seen in the city due to
which a good
momentum is maintained here. Sir, I
would like to know your opinion on ICC Lombard's today's action, in
this way, although it has slowed down a bit now,
but the momentum is still
maintained here, how are you looking at this
news and will it continue here for a few days in the coming time
or do
you think that it should come down a little
to 1400, from Motilal Oswal's side it
is currently stating around 1200,
9.9% is still visible,
Vipul ji, by the way, if you talk about this company overall, there were
talks that ICC may
reduce its stock,
such things were being discussed in the market,
but if you
want to increase the stock again, then it is quite positive.  As per the
news, whenever a promoter
makes a stake in a company, it is quite
positive for investor sentiment.
I also like Lok stock a lot
because it is in a mis segment. In a listed
company, you will find two to three such stocks
which you will see in general insurance in this segment. The
stock is
much better, it is quite good, but because
today there has been a momentum of 8 to 9%, so
you should wait for a little decline. If it is available near 1150 also, then there will be
good levels to accumulate.
In this space, in such groups,
I am seeing good momentum in such potential also.
If you want to buy for training, then you can
go for ICC Prudential
because sentiment wise this is what is called.
JB also has a big stake in some company,
maybe in his other company also, the
print company is
seeing good momentum. I
wanted to buy for trading.
For ICC, if you want to buy ICC General Insurance, then
wait for the price of 1150. If it comes above 1150, then you can
buy and go ahead. So in the
meantime, leave this aside for now.
Now let's discuss a little about Mahindra and Mahindra
because the
results of Mahindra have come, sir, firstly the
autopack is quite good, we are seeing
that the momentum is maintained here and
apart from this, even today after the results, it has
come on the radar of many brokerage houses, many people are
seeing a positive side in it, now sir the
profit of the company is big, it has increased by around 22% to
around 1500 49 crores and at the same time
if we look at the company,
today it is better than expected,
now how are you seeing the
overall auto sector, your opinion and the
way in which the company
is quite aggressive about it and
many launches of the company are going to come on Mahindra,
what will be your opinion on Mahindra, it is
also in the list and we have suggested this stock many times, the
results were
quite excellent, I am seeing it,
if you see the stock slowly it is going to go to 1400 or 1450, the
stock should go  Because the
results are very good, you are still
far away, so there is still a lot of progress left
in the stock, so you can ride it,
I am still seeing a momentum of ₹100,
you can do it in the short term,
you can see it in 20 to 25 days also, so the
stock is quite good, it is trading
around 1325, brother, check the stock on current,
I felt that the levels of 1450 1470 are good,
here also there is good momentum,
you should keep an eye on the targets given here and I have already given it,
Prajapati ji is present with us, but
I was going to discuss one more stock and that of
Window Pharma, Prajapati ji, hello, wait,
okay sir, I was going to discuss one stock, let's
end the discussion on this, the results of Arvindo Pharma have
also come, sir, they have also been quite good, the
profit of the company has been 505 crores
and the income of the company, if we see, it has been
676479 crores, the results have been good
and there are good results.  As a result, there
is a positive trend here as well on Arvindo Pharma.
What is your view on overall pharma, sir, and especially
Arvindo Pharma. Today we are seeing a
weakness of around 80% here.
In the last 6 months, the
company has given a return of around 30%
and in the last one year, if we talk about this year, then
we are seeing 39-40%
returns from January till now.
You can see in the chart
what kind of recovery has happened after the collection. There are still
possibilities of some decline.
How are you looking at the fundamentals?
Absolutely, the fundamentals have improved a lot. According to the
government data, it was released
for the pharma industry and it
was quite positive for this company as well.
You can see the plus thing in the stock price as well.
From around 400, the stock has come back to around ₹600,
minimum. I think,
people of Perfect were around 400
in the web and right now it is
trading around 600. According to this  The results have also
been good. I feel that if the stock
can gain some more momentum,
580 will be a good target for short term traders.
Then if the stock goes below the target, then there is
a short term weakness and strength in the stock.
As far as the target is concerned,
I am expecting the stock to go up till 676-75.
If someone has bought it, then a stoppage of 580
must be placed. I am
expecting a rally till 670 and a rally in the stock and there is
strength in the stock.
Come on, Prajapati ji is waiting for us.
Praja ji, Prajapati ji, hello,
where are you from Sir? You are
from Delhi, I
get some relief from the heat
but after that there is humidity and floods.
What do you do, Sir,
I am in service.
Sir,
how many shares of yours are there today, Sir, have you brought it to you?
What did you tell me? This is being
seen in the entire financial sector.
What should be done? Your
chart is quite strong. One thing to keep in
mind is that the momentum is
quite good and it is
trading almost around the level for the upside, so stop loss.
First of all, keep this in mind because you have to take this
contract rate,
if you take it in any police then
it is considered contracted, the level of 1070 is acting as a
resistance in the stock,
if it crosses that level then a
big momentum can be created in the stock, so
first of all the stock should be placed at 1070,
if there is a stop
level bridge above 1070 then exit your put position from
there, you can get a big movement up to
1100, second and keep this thing in
mind because their option is
of June, so there is still a lot of time value
left with them,
their time value will not decline much for the next one week,
so they have time for one week to
hold, as soon as the first week of
June is over, their time value will
start decreasing and as soon as it
goes to mid week then you will
see the time value coming down, the
stock should definitely be plus in it, if the stock of 1070 is
plus, then
exit from your position, second thing if
next week  Even if your price does
not come, you should exit the option
because the time value will decrease a lot,
so even if the stock does not move, your
value will still be seen to have come down. So
do two things, keep a stop of 1070 in mind. Second,
in this week, tell me any two stocks from this post,
whether technical or
fundamental, whatever the reason, you have selected,
and whether you have seen 400 there, or some other reason,
due to which
you are advising to buy here,
okay, select both the stocks technically,
both are scouted stocks, the first stock
is MFL, I am seeing a
big breakout in the stock after many weeks, it is trading
around 695 697, I feel that
this stock
can reach the level above 750 again, so
buy Max Financial, it is looking at 680,
I am seeing a target of 755,
you can see a target above it, the second
stock will be this, I took a contract between
and the results of the stock are also in blue today
I feel that the results of this stock should
come in the market after today, that is
IRCTC is around 641, this top is also
appearing to me, it can show a good momentum on the upside, the
stock may take a loss of 610,
targets of 678 to 680 can be seen,
keep one thing in mind in this because
today's result is, it can remain in one stock, but
technically it looks very strong to me
and the breakup of inverted heading shoulder is
visible in the stock, that is why
I have picked the stock, definitely pay attention to the business,
if the results are good then it is
possible that you may see a big momentum in the stock, a big
momentum can be seen in the stock, they have told
what is visible in the chats technically,
once again please
bring on the screen these two stocks
which have been advised to buy here, a
large number of our Darshans come wait for the
segment, our Max Financial
Services, where we had seen that the results were
very good, Arun told about the technical reasons,
but the results were very excellent and
after that  There is also a good momentum from this
in Max Financial Services. We had
discussed this in this program
during Bhujing stock and many fears,
many of our experts are also positive about it
and even now there is a buying trend here
and the technical is looking strong.
Arun ji has a target of 755 and 680,
you can keep a stop loss here and go ahead. The
stock is trading around 700,
Arun ji believes that this is what should be done, keep an
eye on the results and if the result is
positive then
more momentum can be seen increasing here. The
price of Star Plus 610 is around
₹26 below and the current price is around ₹40-42 above this way, so
according to the school, we are coming out with very good
targets here and
in the entire railway stock itself we have seen that the
momentum is maintained, the result is awaited and if the
result becomes favorable then I think there is
very good momentum as we have seen
in Arab and all the stocks, with a lot of speed.  It has been
seen that if the results are good
then there is a possibility of a lot of rise here.
Arun has
shared this because both
are trading recommendations and the rest of the stocks discussed can be with
our clients
in any of my personal portfolios. Thank you very much Sir,
thank you very much for
giving your valuable time to join today's program
and for making this discussion very important.
Thank you very much
[Music]